CBS影业出品
命运早已锻就利刃...
铸剑者只是顺应其形
— 埃斯库罗斯 (古希腊悲剧作家)
命运
人族帝国
她回来了
She's back!
她回家了
She's home!
菲莉帕回家了
Philippa came home!
两年过去了
Two years,
一切都还和我记忆中一样
and everything looks exactly as I remember.
我本以为自己永远没法回家了
I never thought I would see this place again.
这次我们有18人
There were 18 of us this time.
都是从帝国的各个角落
Culled from every corner of the Empire
被抓到地球参加比赛
and brought to Terra for the contest.
我们被告知 接下来的几年里
We were told that only one of us would survive
我们当中只有一个人能活下来
the years to come.
只有一个孩子
One child
能代表最纯粹的地球血统
the purest expression of the Terran identity.
他们让我们互相残杀
They pitted us against each other.
过了一个又一个月 人数逐渐减少
And month by month, our numbers dwindled.
那 你赢了吗
Did... did you win?
比赛结束了吗
Is it over?
还有两个人活着
Two of us still live.
桑和我
San and me.
我和桑
Me and San.
我们虽为两人
We are two
但为一体
but one.
直至永恒
Forever.
竞赛当中禁止出现「朋友」这个词
The word "friend" was forbidden during the contest,
但我们在别人听不到的时候向对方耳语说出这个词
but we whispered it to each other when no one could hear.
桑和我将我们的技能结合起来
San and I combined our skills
一起对付监察者和其他参赛者
against the proctor and the other contestants.
但你们当中只有一个人能成为皇帝
But only one of you could be emperor.
还剩下最后一个任务
One task remains.
最先完成任务的人就可以统治帝国
The first to complete it rules the Empire,
而另一个人
and the other spends the rest of their life
将终生侍奉新皇
in servitude to the new emperor.
你要做什么
What do you have to do?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你做了什么
What did you do?!
一切旧日牵绊 皆不可再续
No ties to the old life are permitted.
人族的帝皇唯忠于职责
An emperor can only be loyal to duty.
如此帝国方能强盛
Thus does the Empire remain strong.
如此帝国方能扩张
Thus does it grow.
妈妈
Mom.
菲莉帕
Philippa.
你完成了你的对手无法下手的任务
You succeeded where your competitor could not.
把他带过来
Bring him here.
桑缺乏勇气 没能通过最后的试炼
San did not have the strength to pass the final test.
现在 他的村庄仍在烈火中燃烧 昭示着他的懦弱
Even now, his village burns as a testament to his cowardice.
我爱你
I love you.
你赢得了比赛
You have won the contest.
宣布你的胜利吧
Claim your victory.
桑  走上前
San, step forward.
现在你的生命只为侍奉于她的足下
You live now only to serve at her heel.
跪下 向主宰你生命的皇帝臣服
Kneel before the one who owns your life.
我们虽为两人
We are two...
但为一体
But one.
不再是了
Not anymore.
菲莉帕·乔久万岁
All hail Philippa Georgiou!
皇帝万岁
All hail the emperor!
万岁 万岁
Hail! Hail!
正在执行加密协议
密钥已认证
（最高优先级讯息 来自总控 发往阿尔法小队领队）
（声纹已认证 简报开始）
我是总控
This is Control
有一条发给阿尔法小队领队的最高优先级讯息
with a priority message for Alpha Team Leader.
你们的新目标是菲莉帕·乔久皇帝
Your subject is Emperor Philippa Georgiou,
人族帝国的前任统治者
former ruler of the Terran Empire.
人族帝国存在于一个平行宇宙中
It's in a parallel universe
在已知历史记录中
with the most criminal population
该帝国的臣民最为残暴
in recorded history.
即使在那个宇宙 乔久仍能以暴政完全掌控帝国的每个角落
Even there, Georgiou had the market cornered on atrocities.
2257年 她被带到我们的宇宙
In 2257, she was brought to our universe
并加入31区
and joined Section 31,
但几年后 我们失去了联络
but after a few years, we lost contact.
联络丢失
（乔久目前状态 位置已确认 化名：杜·弗朗克女士）
（恐袭威胁 一级优先级）
（卡坦条约 禁止联邦势力跨越边界）
（警告 目标极端危险）
近日 我们在星联边境外的区域
Recently, Georgiou was spotted using an alias
发现菲莉帕·乔久以化名出现
in the border territory outside Federation space,
该地正是我们追踪黑市新威胁的关键区域
where we're tracking a new threat on the black market.
接下来的任务，就交给你们了
This is where your team comes in.
联邦签订的条约禁止我们跨越边界
Federation treaty forbids us from crossing over that border,
也就意味着星际舰队不能暗中行事
which means Starfleet cannot get its hands dirty.
你和你31区的队伍将前往与乔久联络
You and your 31 team will go in, make contact with Georgiou
发现并控制那个威胁
to help identify and neutralize the threat.
但需注意
But make no mistake
恶犬咬人 多加小心
this dog bites, so watch your backs.
你们只有24小时的时间完成任务
You have 24 hours to complete the mission.
动身吧
Get to work.
通讯结束
星际迷航：31区
（星际迷航中国字幕组译制）
星历 1292.4
星际联邦领空之外
（加密传讯1）
（巴拉姆空间站上的一夜）
杜·弗朗克女士
Madame du Franc?
蜜月套房里出了个小事故
Small incident in the honeymoon suite.
似乎是一位新娘
I'm afraid the bride molted
在快到高潮的时候蜕皮了
just as things were coming to a climax.
维吉尔 说重点
Virgil,get to the point.
我派出了一支生化小队 并致以你的吊唁
I sent a biohazard team and your condolences.
另外 有一位顾客想和你说句话
Also, there's a customer hoping for a word with you.
他已经喝了不少 但看起来还是很清醒
He seems entirely sober but quite intoxicating.
维罗妮克·杜·弗朗克女士同意见你
Madame Veronique du Franc will see you.
阿洛克·萨哈  这位是维罗妮克·杜·弗朗克女士
Alok Sahar, Madame Veronique du Franc.
杜·弗朗克女士一般只接受预约洽谈
Madame du Franc normally does business by appointment.
那我想预约一下
I'd like to make an appointment.
噢 这位绅士想预约一下
Oh, the gentleman would like to make an appointment.
就约现在
Now.
他说就约现在 女士
Now, madame.
（法语）
Impossible.
她说不可能
先退下吧 维吉尔
Au revoir, Virgil.
这玩意儿是非法的
That is illegal.
但能赚大钱
And that makes money.
我这里是声誉良好的生意场所
This is a reputable establishment.
据我所知可不是这样
Not what I heard.
我们为什么不去你的办公室讨论呢
Why don't we discuss it in your office?
我为什么要带你去我的办公室呢 阿洛克·萨哈
Why would I take you to my office, Alok Sahar?
因为这玩意儿得自己试试
Because it's a hands-on experience.
我所到之处
♪ Everywhere I go ♪
人尽皆知
♪ Everybody knows... ♪
悦耳蓟
Dulcet thistle.
悦耳蓟已经灭绝了
Dulcet thistle's extinct.
我有很多存货
I've got a dozen keys of this stuff.
你要来点吗
Have you partaken?
这将是我为数不多的几次初体验
This would be one of my few first times.
来一杯潘趣酒
Packs a punch.
快乐的一杯
A happy punch.
干杯
Bottoms up.
敬赚钱
To money.
敬你
To you.
好了 别说废话了
Now, let's cut the shit.
31区来我的空间站干什么
What is Section 31 doing in my space station?
你觉得我会认不出来一个特工吗
Hmm? You think I don't know an agent when I see one?
你带领着一个六人小队
You're heading up a team of six operatives,
分散在这个酒吧里
and they're all over the bar.
有一个查莫人*
There's the Chameloid,
（* 电影6《星际迷航6: 未来之城》中出现的玛缇娅就是查莫人）
这个绿血变形人
a green-blooded shape-shifter,
假装在与一个德尔塔人*调情寻欢
trying to muster sexy time with a Deltan,
（* 在电影1《星际迷航1: 无限太空》中出现，他们的生理特质使其对大多数种族有着非凡魅力）
一个行走的情欲陷阱
a walking honey trap
31区用来转移注意力的惯用伎俩
31's obviously using as a distraction.
可实际上查莫人是银河系里唯一
Except Chameloids are the only species in the galaxy
对德尔塔人的魅惑能力保持免疫的种族
immune to Deltan sexy time charm.
然后是那个穿着一身高端器械的家伙
Then there's the guy with all the high-end mech,
傻站在后面 显得好像他有脑子似的
standing in the back, looking like he has thoughts.
机械生命 有的可不只是蛮力
Mech life, it ain't just about the brute force.
实际上就是头脑简单 四肢发达
I'm gonna say heavy on artillery, low on IQ.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
还有那位瓦肯人
And we can't forget the Vulcan,
被舞台表演逗得哈哈大笑
laughing way too hard at the stage banter.
鉴于瓦肯人从来不笑
And since Vulcans never laugh,
他要么也是个白痴
he's either an idiot, too,
（* 瓦肯人每七年经历一次的发情时期）
要么就是在庞发*期间脑子变得不正常了
or lost his mind during pon farr and went insane.
拜托 那明明很好笑啊
Oh, come on. That was funny.
还有你安排给他那个特别正经的人类搭档
And the very serious human you stuck him with...
你控制一下自己
Reel it in anytime.
她看着就是一副苦大仇深的样子
...she's got a stick so far up her backside,
一开口就能听出来
it's coming out her mouth.
冷静一点
Just reel it in.
那位是
That would be
加勒特上尉*
Lieutenant Garrett.
（* 瑞秋·加勒特 未来进取号-C的舰长 见《下一代》3x15）
星际舰队的
Starfleet.
无趣到死
Where fun goes to die.
你找我花了不少时间啊
It took you long enough to find me.
只要你留在巴拉姆空间站
We knew that having you here on the Baraam
对我们来说 总有一天会派上用场
would be valuable to us one day.
好吧 我不得不说我一点儿也不感动
Well, I'm not feeling motivated to be valuable
我只为自己所用
to anyone but myself.
今夜请说愿意
♪ Say yes tonight ♪
一切都可应允
♪ Say yes to everything... ♪
所以 我们就这么开始谈判吗
So, is this where we start negotiating?
那要看情况了
Hmm, that depends.
你们是何时发现我的
How long have you known about me?
从你自前任站主那儿接手开始 我们就知道了
Ever since you took over from the previous owner,
而那位站主到现在依然下落不明
who we still haven't found.
其他的前站主也是
Well, all of.
这可不是我干的
That wasn't me.
乔久皇帝
Emperor Georgiou,
我完全有权逮捕你
I am authorized to arrest you
抹除你的记忆
and wipe your mind clean.
但是话又说回来 我心里还是觉得
But then again, there's a part of me
你更应当背负那些不堪回忆而活
that wants you to live with your memories.
尤其种族灭绝的那些
The genocidal ones.
你有权逮捕我
Being authorized to arrest me
不等于你有能力逮捕我
isn't the same as being able to arrest me.
你真的希望31区 希望我
You really want Section 31-- want me--
不止不休地追着你吗
dogging you until the end of time?
无聊
Boring.
往事如影随形啊
The past always catches up with you.
既然我们都不希望如此
And as much as both of us might hate it,
我会帮你个忙
I'm doing you a favor.
最后一次任务
One last mission.
听着
Listen.
你相信命运吗
Do you believe in fate?
我信
Because I do.
你无处可逃
You can't hide from it.
乔久 你在这里什么都不是
You're nothing here, Georgiou.
现在我给你一个机会
I'm giving you a chance to get back in.
参与这场跨越银河的行动
In on the action on a galactic scale.
别再逃避了
Stop running from it.
成为你本该成为的人
Be who you are.
或者就在这个酒吧待一辈子
Or stay and tend bar for eternity.
那就抓紧开始吧
Let's get on with it.
菲莉帕·乔久 认识一下我的团队
Philippa Georgiou, meet my team.
这是梅尔
This is Melle.
泽弗
Zeph.
你看起来像一把瑞士军刀
You look like a Swiss Army knife.
等等
Uh, hold on.
我不知道那是什么意思
I don't know what that means, but I'm not gonna
但我不可能傻站在这里被你侮辱
just stand here and get insulted.
我没说你
I'm not talking about you.
我是说你的装甲
I'm talking about your suit.
鉴于你是新来的
Um, you're new,
所以我就解释这一回
so I'm gonna just explain this one time
当你在说我这套装甲的时候
that when you are talking about the suit,
就是在说我
you're talking about Zeph.
泽弗有点机械变形障碍症 大概
Zeph suffers from what we call mecha dysmorphia.
我也许不知道那是啥意思
And I may not know what that is,
但我也不接受你这说法
but I'm also not gonna take that from you,
小夸 我觉得你冒犯了我
Quas, and personally I'm offended.
-我觉得你应当知道  -这挺对的
- I think you should know... - Well, it's accurate.
你不能诊断我得了什么 你不是医生
It's not a diagnosis. You're not a doctor.
泽弗 泽弗 泽弗
Zeph. Zeph, Zeph!
-他知道 他知道 别吵了 -好吧
- He knows. He knows. He knows. - Okay, fine.
他知道
He knows.
-他明白的 他明白的 -是的
- He gets it. He gets it. - Yes.
行了 那位瓦肯人呢
Okay, what about that Vulcan?
没人跟她说吗
Nobody told her?
你说这个吗 正跟你说话的这个东西
This? The thing you're talking to?
这个瓦肯外表不过是台机器
The Vulcan's just a machine.
我在里面
I'm inside.
操控它
Driving.
我通过体内的备用驾驶舱控制这具身体
I control the body from a backup vehicle.
这是我专门用来在狭窄空间里进出的小玩意
Yeah, something I use to get into tight spots.
你好啊
Hi there.
我是法兹
I'm Fuzz.
法兹是纳米人
Fuzz is a Nanokin.
一个天性爱玩的家伙
Real fun-loving guy.
你好
Hello.
除非他哪天不感兴趣了
Except for when he's not.
然后他就会变成一个易暴易怒的人了
Then he's deranged with an anger management problem.
你该说完第一句就闭嘴的 夸西
Well, you could've stopped at the first thing, Quasi.
一个非法制造的瓦肯型运输载体
A bootleg Vulcan conveyance?
你肯定在黑市上见过不少了不得的东西
You must see cool stuff on the black market.
纳米人都是天生的拾荒者
Nanokins are pretty scavengery.
31区在废弃的船只上发现了虫害
31 made first contact when we
然后才有了第一次接触
discovered an infestation on a derelict ship.
夸西
Quasi.
啊 糟了
Oh, shit.
夸西 你再说一遍「虫害」试试看
Say "infestation" one more time, Quasi.
叫我拾荒者 你这袋没形状的烟灰
Say "scavenger," you sack of amorphous soot!
我 我一顺口就说出来了
I-I s-- I heard it as soon as I said it.
我真想好好揍你一顿
I will kick your ass
直到你变成一团液体的…
until you cannot form a solid mass of...
法兹 情绪控制一下
Fuzz. Fuzz. Lock it down.
我已经够冷静了
I am locked down.
我被困在一个巨大的瓦肯机器脑袋里
I'm trapped inside a giant robot Vulcan head.
此刻没人比我更「冷静」了
No one is more locked down than me right now!
纳米人情绪光谱不太稳定
Nanokins have a wonky emotional spectrum.
不不不不行
No, no, no, no, no, no,
不许用居高临下的态度对我 梅尔
I will not be condescended to, Melle,
尤其是你 因为说实话
particularly not by you, because honest...
我爱你 你就是一切
I love you. You are everything.
- 你喜欢我复杂的情绪光谱吗 - 法兹
- Does my spectrum work for you? - Fuzz.
- 我意思是 你是认真的吗 还是说…  -法兹
- I mean, like, like, are you into it or...  - Fuzz!
法兹
Fuzz!
她在侮辱你 老兄
She's insulting you, pal.
我就知道德尔塔人又会做他们德尔塔人的那一套
I know Deltans are gonna do their Deltan thing,
但是自尊自爱点吧 伙计
but have a little self-respect, would you?
能继续任务了吗
Can we continue?
然后这位是瑞秋·加勒特上尉
And that's Lieutenant Rachel Garrett.
她仅为这次任务被临时派往31区
She is detailed to Section 31 for this one mission only.
上尉 你得罪了谁才被派来这个秘密组织?
Who did you piss off to get stuck in black ops, Lieutenant?
派个星际舰队的人进来是确保我们行事合规
Starfleet is here to make sure we color inside the lines.
我参与本次行动的目的是保卫联邦
Starfleet is here to defend the Federation,
维持和平状态并确保不发生谋杀事件
keep the peace and make sure no one commits murder.
那你呢
And you?
等一下
One moment.
我认识夸西是因为
Quasi came on my radar
他证明了神经胶质细胞簇的存在
when he proved the existence of glioclusters.
神经胶质细胞簇只存在于理论中
Glioclusters are theoretical.
曾经是
Formerly theoretical.
生命充满无限可能
Life is just branching possibilities.
它们以你能想象的任何方式盛开
You know, they bloom and blossom any way you can imagine.
比如 我现在可能会被你吓倒
For example, I could be intimidated by you right now.
毕竟你杀了那么多人
I mean, after all, you've murdered so many people...
而且你好像能看透我的灵魂
and you seem to be staring right into my soul.
我可以对此做出回应
I could respond to that
或者我可以观察我的感受
or I could observe my feelings right now,
不管它 只做我需要做的事
lock it away and do what I need to do.
或者说
Or...
小夸 选一个好吗
Quas. Pick one. Hmm?
- 好吧 - 有时夸西看到了太多可能性
- Yes. - Sometimes Quasi sees so many options
以至于他的思维可能会有所停滞
he gets brain-freeze.
多谢夸奖呢 梅尔
Thank you, Melle.
夸西 我们能继续了吗
Quasi, can we carry on, please?
我们的目标是达达·诺尔
Our target's name is Dada Noe.
一个有道德底线在哪都存疑的家伙
Dubious moral compass.
在他叛变之前 他在瓦特殖民地经营着一个病理学实验室
Ran a pathology lab on the Watt Colonies before he went rogue.
自那以后 他便开始替人定制生化武器
Since then, he's been designing bioweapons on spec.
诺尔前往巴拉姆空间站是为了
Noe's on his way to the Baraam
把他的最新发明出手给米诺斯最高议会
to sell his latest creation to the Minosian High Council.
目前我们与米诺斯统治体之间并无正式敌对状态
There are no formal hostilities with the Minosian Sway,
但若他们拿到这件武器
but that could change
情况可能会发生变化
if they get their hands on a superweapon.
有任何关于这个超级生物武器的信息吗
Do we know what this bio superweapon is?
没有 但要是诺尔成功出售就坏了
No, but if Dada Noe is selling it, it's bad.
所以你的任务目标就是确保交易不会发生
So you're here to make sure the sale never happens.
怎么做
How?
你对我们行动的发觉确实造成了一些影响
Things went south when you spotted us,
但计划仍然可靠
but the plan is still solid.
首先 阿洛克会
First, Alok was going to...
你说吧
You can say it.
和你亲密接触
Connect. With you.
欢迎
Welcome!
异想天开啊
What a cute idea.
一旦我们适当的分散了你的注意力
Once we had you suitably distracted,
就轮到夸西做他擅长的事了
Quasi would do the other thing Quasi does.
好了 夸西
Okay, Quasi.
麻烦你了
If you would do the honors.
没问题
Absolutely.
我们开始吧
Let's get to work.
欢迎欢迎 达达·诺尔
Welcome, Dada Noe.
这时候法兹会参与进来
This is where Fuzz comes in.
你绝对想不到我能进入多小的地方
You wouldn't believe the tiny spots I can get into.
比如 身体改造组件的内部空间
For example, the inner workings of body modifications.
只要我进入达达的身体改造组件里
Oh, once I fly inside Dada's body mod,
这就是我要发挥作用的时刻
well, then it's time to get to work.
这么多电路
So many circuits.
太多可能出错的东西了
So many things that could go wrong.
我们这位全副武装的十字军战士
Competency crusader here will talk me through
会通过植入物跟我交谈
the tech on the implant.
如果我认为我们通过达达·诺尔的植入物
And if I think we're putting Dada Noe's life in danger
让他生命垂危
by tinkering with that implant,
我会通过星际舰队
I will unleash the full weight of Starfleet
对此次任务施压
on this whole operation.
嘿 我们讨论的可是一个要出售超级武器的家伙
Oy, we're talking about a bloke who's selling superweapons
他会把东西卖给任何有拉蒂金卡的三流恐怖分子
to any third-rate terrorist with a Latinum card.
听仔细了 满脑子废品的家伙
Listen carefully, Junkyard.
星际舰队不执行暗杀任务
Starfleet does not do assassinations.
唉 别再满脑子的惦记着你的最高指导原则了
Ay, don't get your prime directives in a bunch.
不会让你亲自下场弄脏手的
You are not going to get your hands dirty
也不会坏了你升舰长的前程
and mess up your chances of becoming captain.
我可是顶尖科学官
I'm a top-tier science officer.
屁股拧成麻花了
Butt pretzel.
就是个死板精
Tight-ass.
真是太不尊重人了
So disrespectful.
只要加勒特和法兹切断了组件的链接
Soon as Garrett and Fuzz sever that link...
他就随便我们拿捏了
...he'll be under our control,
我会和泽弗一起制服他
and I'll take him down with the help of Zeph.
一下搞定
That's what I call a hit.
只需一下
One.
达达·诺尔会被拘留 他的病原体会被没收
Dada Noe and his pathogen will be in custody
这一切会在卖家出现在巴拉姆空间站之前就完成
before the buyers can even show up to the Baraam.
速战速决
And we are in and out.
呃
Mm.
算了
Meh.
啥
Meh?
我有个更简单的办法
I have a simpler idea.
表情很绝望 我看的出来
♪ Desperate, I can tell ♪
所有的祈求
♪ All that begging ♪
都像是为你量身定做的
♪ Suits you well. ♪
现在打爆我的手机
♪ Blowing up my phone now ♪
我向上 你低头
♪ Going up, you bow down ♪
看看是谁需要谁
♪ Look at who needs who... ♪
欢迎欢迎 达达·诺尔先生
Welcome, Monsieur Dada Noe.
您的到来使巴拉姆空间站蓬荜生辉
We're honored to have you here at the Baraam.
我是维罗妮卡·杜·弗朗克 这里的店主
I am Veronique du Franc, the proprietor.
我早就预约我的套间了吧
I told them to have my suite ready.
当然 先生
Mais oui, monsieur.
请允许我带您到房间里
May I escort you to your quarters?
请随我来
Come.
我们有最好的…
We have the most exquisite...
我简直不敢相信你会信任这个反社会的疯子
I can't believe you're trusting this sociopath.
上尉
Well, Lieutenant,
你做好自己的事
you got to do what you got to do,
我知道怎么跟反社会疯子打交道
and I'm kind of familiar with sociopaths.
我说了别带我来
I said don't bring me.
我想您的旅程一切顺利 先生
I trust your trip was without incident, monsieur.
你的团队倒是帮我把一切都打点好了
Well, your people made everything easy.
不胜荣幸
Our pleasure.
我们到了
Here we are.
太俗气了
So tacky.
但我想这就是你出名的地方
But I guess that's what you're known for.
这是什么？
What's this?
这东西叫相位转移器
It's called a phase pod.
我的某位客户送给我的礼物
A client of mine gave it to me as a gift,
我自己也有一个
and I got one for myself, too.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
宇宙中的一切
Everything in the universe vibrates
都以特定的波长振动
on a certain wavelength.
该死
Damn it.
把箱子还给我
Give me back my case.
我拒绝
No.
维修费从你的押金里出
That's coming out of your security deposit.
相位转移器则会改变
The phase pod changes the wavelength
接触到的任何东西的物质波长
of whatever they touch.
我和你不在同一相位 你也不和我在同一相位
I am out of phase with you, and you're out of phase with me.
但是我 跟你的箱子在同一相位
I am, however, in phase with your case.
然后我会把它拿走
And I will be taking it with me.
你根本不知道你挑起了什么
You have no idea what you've started.
哎呀
Whoopsie.
不错嘛
Impressive.
你真的是普通人类吗
Are you sure you're human?
多数时候是
Most days.
谢谢你
Thank you.
把箱子给我
Give me the case.
你是谁
Who are you?
他从那儿走了 那儿那儿 走那边
He went that way. That way, that way, that way!
哇 外星人
Oh, aliens.
还是裸体的
Naked aliens.
泽弗 快追
Go, Zeph, go.
他往休息室去了 天哪 他们走得真快
He's headed to the lounge. Man, they're moving fast.
梅尔 他朝你来了
Melle, he's coming to you.
哎呀
Yikes.
没事没事 我还好
No, it's okay. I'm all right.
梅尔 有看到目标吗
Melle, you got him?
看到了
Got him.
哎呀
Ooh-la-la!
嗨 亲爱的
Ay, amor.
不可能
That's not possible.
它已经被我销毁了
I had that destroyed.
不
No. No!
这不可能
It's not possible.
你知道那件武器
You knew that weapon.
是什么
What is it?
回答我
行 那就来硬的
Fine. The hard way.
永恒的祈求者恳请觐见
The Eternal Supplicant begs approach.
（人族帝国）
（上辈子）
永恒的祈求者恳请觐见
The Eternal Supplicant begs approach.
准了
You have my permission.
参见至高无上的女皇陛下
All hail Her Most Imperial Majesty,
崇上国母
Mother of the Fatherland,
- 瓦肯领主 - 你带来的是什么
- Overlord of Vulc... - What is it?
它完成了 陛下
It is finished, Your Majesty.
我的工程师们在哪
Where are my engineers?
他们 他们在完工后结束了自己的生命
They... they took their own lives upon completion.
你在为谁流泪 桑
Who is the tear for, San?
说
Speak.
是为您 陛下
It is for you, Majesty.
这都是
It is all...
为了您
...for you.
我再问你 桑
I asked you a question, San.
你为何为我而哭
Why do you cry for me?
看着我
Look at me.
你还记得我们是谁吗
Do you remember who we were?
在这一切之前
Before all this.
好奇的男孩
The curious boy.
天真的女孩
The innocent girl.
我只记得我的失败 陛下
I only remember my failure, Majesty.
别对我撒谎
Don't lie to me.
为了活下去 我们付出了别人无法想象的代价
We were the only ones who could understand the cost to stay alive.
我们是一个集体
We made a team.
彼此依靠 不可分割
We needed each other, didn't we?
记得那时我们是靠着什么话语 彼此支撑着活下来的吗
What did we say to carry each other through, to survive together?
我们虽为两人
We are two...
但为一体
But one.
我们虽为两人 但为一体
We are two but one.
如果我说
If I said then,
「我们逃跑吧」
"Let's run away,
「逃离这场竞争」
"let's flee this competition
「以及把我们和人族联系在一起的一切」
and everything that binds us to Terra,"
你会说什么呢
what would you have said?
您问这个问题的时机 比您认为的更富意味
The timing of your question is more poetic than you know.
我会答应您
I would have said yes.
只会在当时
Then.
那么现在呢
But now?
您本可以在您的治下创造一些美好的东西
You could have made something beautiful with your reign.
然而 您却选择了让人制造此物
Instead, you chose to build this.
这意味着我熟知的那个天真女孩
That means that innocent girl I knew,
她已经
she has been...
死了
...murdered.
怎么回事
What is this?
你
You...
你服用了一样的毒药?
You took the same poison?
不 我不许你死
No! I forbid you to die!
没有人愿意活在
No one wants to live
您的统治中 皇帝
in your world, Emperor.
你就是个怪物
You are a monster!
这是什么令人愉快的地方
And what delightful place is this?
一个安全屋
A safe house.
但对你而言也许不是
But maybe not so safe for you.
既然你是31区的
You are Section 31.
你为什么不拷问我以获取答案
Why aren't you torturing answers out of me?
你是个暴君
You're a tyrant.
货真价实的
A real one.
折磨起不到半点作用
Torture wouldn't work.
你怎么会这么了解我这种人呢
How do you know so much about people like me?
是在哪里学来的暴君手段 而且学得很到位
You learned tyranny somewhere, and you learned hard.
藏着掖着 只证明了你的软弱
If you have to hide it, that's a weakness.
而我 不能容许搭档有这种弱点
And I can't have that in a partner.
我们可算不上搭档
We're not partners.
不是吗
No?
我可是帮了大忙了
I've been very helpful.
你的计划行不通
You had a plan that couldn't work.
而我给了你更好的
I gave you a better one.
你让我尝到了那种刺激
You gave me a taste of the action,
还明知道我会上瘾
knowing I'd want more.
你需要我
You need me.
你选择了我
You chose me.
为什么呢
Why?
不管你认为你的任务是什么
Whatever you believed your mission was,
这远比你想象的更糟糕
it's worse than you thought.
事关数亿万生命 时间紧迫
Billions of lives are at stake, and time is short.
你先让我了解你 我才能告诉你
Tell me you, and I will tell you me.
要想合作 我得知根知底
The only way this works is if I know exactly
说出你的身份
who I'm dealing with.
我也不属于这个时代
I'm not from this time, either.
我出生于20世纪的地球
I was born on Earth, 20th century.
这么说你已经350岁高龄了
You are 350 years old?
差不多
More or less.
大部分时间我在冬眠舱里
I slept most of that time.
在我被流放之后
After my exile.
优生战争
The Eugenics Wars.
强化人
Augments...
夺走了我的星球
took my planet.
我的家乡
My home.
当时我们差不多有十个人在战斗
There was maybe ten of us who fought.
我认识的人不是挨了一枪就是挨了一刀
Everyone I knew either took a bullet or a blade.
我也还以颜色
But I gave some back.
这让她注意到了我
She noticed me.
那个屠杀我家人的强化人
The Augment who slaughtered my family.
他们叫她 被标记的吉里
They called her Giri the Marked.
她收留了我
She took me in.
让我比任何人类都强大
Made me stronger than any human should be.
她把我撕成碎片
She ripped me apart
然后把我重塑成了她军队里的又一个强化人
and turned me into another Augment for her army.
我做了很多可怕的事
And I did terrible things.
却是为你这样的怪物效力
All for a monster like you.
因为对于暴君来说 永远只有一个选择
Because for tyrants, there is only one choice:
杀戮
murder.
但你却没杀掉我
You haven't killed me.
暂时而已
Yet.
我之所以能认出那个武器
I recognized the weapon because
因为它是我下令造的
I ordered it to be built.
召集你的人手
Gather your people.
每个人都得派上用场
We're gonna need every one of them.
（加密传讯2）
（天赐之物）
在我的宇宙里
In my universe,
阴谋重重 政敌环伺
there were always plotters.
政变层出不穷
Always a coup.
所以我造了一件武器来终结所有威胁
So I built a weapon to end all threats.
我称之为
I called it
「天赐之物」
the Godsend.
它会引发一种连锁反应
It triggers a chain reaction,
就像病毒一样在群星间传播
like a virus passing between planets.
所到之处 一切都将化为灰烬
Everything in its path incinerates.
整个象限都会消失
An entire quadrant would be lost.
如果我的敌人成功杀死了我
If my enemies managed to kill me,
那也不会有东西留给他统治
there would be nothing left to rule.
有个小问题
Yeah, hi. Quick question.
不好意思
Sorry.
就一个很小很小的问题
Yeah, no. Uh, just a qu-- it's just a quick one.
这是天赐之物还是天赐之暮
Is it Godsend or God's End?
天赐之物还是天赐之暮
Godsend or God's End?
我不明白你说的有什么区别
I don't hear a difference in what you're saying.
听不出来吗 「物」和「暮」
Really? Really? Godsend. God's End.
我还是没听明白
Yeah, I'm still not getting it.
天赐之物是...
The Godsend is...
噢 天赐之物 我现在听清楚了
Wait, Godsend. I hear it now.
-天赐之物 不是暮 -物
- It's Godsend. No apostrophe. - Send.
天赐之物就在这个宇宙
The Godsend is here.
怎么会 那可是另一个宇宙的物品
How? It's from another universe.
我不知道 但那个人刚刚就拿着它
I don't know, but that man had it.
你以为是达达·诺伊的那个人
The one that you think is Dada Noe.
我们都知道是达达·诺伊的那个人
The one we know is Dada Noe.
不 他不可能是你们的达达·诺伊
No, he's not your Dada Noe. He can't be.
他来自人族帝国
He's from the Terran Empire,
是他把天赐之物带来这里
and he brought the Godsend here.
不然他根本不可能知道那到底是什么
That's the only way he can know about it.
既然我们已经抓到他了
And since we have him locked up tight,
我要亲自审讯他
I'll interrogate him.
绝对不行 不能信这个女人说的话
No, no, no. We cannot trust a single word this woman says.
是啊
Yeah.
她害死了梅尔
She cost us Melle.
只有她知道我们面对的是什么人
She's the only one who knows what we're dealing with.
也就是她自己说的 小兄弟
Yeah, well, so she says, little bro.
小?
Little?
这是身材羞辱
Scale-shamer!
微生物比恐龙更长寿
Microbes outlasted dinosaurs!
冷静点 我要说的是
Calm your boots. What I'm saying is...
我要尿在你的装甲上 直到你全身生锈
I will piss in your suit until you go all rusty like!
这一切都是她搞砸的
...that she's the reason this is all bollixed up.
她导致了梅尔的死
She's the reason Melle's dead,
她也是我们被派来这的原因
and she's the reason we're in the ass end of the galaxy.
听好了
Listen up.
乔久和我回船上去
Georgiou and I are gonna go back to the ship.
达达·诺伊是我们与天赐之物的唯一联系
Dada Noe is our only link to the Godsend,
所以我们要找他谈谈
so we're gonna have a little chat with him.
干什么
What?
她叫菲利帕·乔久
Her name is Philippa Georgiou,
至高无上的女皇陛下
Her Most Imperial Majesty.
崇上国母
Mother of the Fatherland.
瓦肯领主
Overlord of Vulcan.
克罗诺斯征服者 安多利女王
Dominus of Qo'noS, Regina Andor,
菲利帕·乔久·奥古斯都·伊波尼亚斯·塞塔瑞斯
Philippa Georgiou Augustus Iaponius Centarius.
酷
Cool.
配薯条的吗
That come with fries?
很好笑 对吧
That was good, right?
好吧
Okay.
每次你不直接回答她的问题
Every time you don't answer her questions directly,
女皇陛下就会狠狠地打你的脸
Her Majesty will punch you in your face.
好吧
Fine.
我是达达
I'm Dada.
达达·诺伊 先念达达 再是诺伊
Dada Noe. Just Dada, then Noe.
就是这样 没有中间
That's it. No in-betweens.
然后 我
And I, uh...
我以前在瓦特殖民地开过一家病理学实验室
I used to run a pathology lab in the Watt Colonies.
搞什么鬼
What the shit, man?!
你明明说揍我脸的会是她
You said that she was gonna be doing the face punching!
现在我俩都说谎了 你不是那个达达
So now we both have lied. You are not that Dada.
你是那些人口中说的他的镜像版本
You're what these people call his Mirror.
你来自人族帝国
You came here from the Terran Empire,
而且还带来了天赐之物
and you brought the Godsend.
什么天赐之物
What's the Godsend?
我自己的军事委员会曾想要废黜我
My own war council tried to depose me.
你知道我是怎么说服元帅开口的吗
Do you know how I convinced the field marshal to talk?
我曾是个管理员
I was an administrator
在帝国里的武器设施工作
at an Imperial weapons facility on Terra.
没错
Uh, yeah.
天赐之物被存放在我管理的设施中
The Godsend was stored at my facility.
大多数人认为这只是一个传说
Most thought it was a legend,
但我知道这是真的
but I knew it was real.
所以你想卖掉它
So you tried to sell it.
是 是的
Yeah, yeah.
我想靠得来的收益安静地生活在这里
I wanted to live here quietly on its proceeds.
你是怎么来到我们的宇宙的
How did you get to our universe?
当时发生了一场离子风暴
There was an ion storm.
实际上是两场
Two of them, actually.
它们像对好了表一样准时相遇
And when they converged, which they do like clockwork,
撕裂了帝国边界某处的时空
they ripped something open on the fringes of the Empire--
他们称之为异象
an anomaly, they called it--
但这实际上是一条通道
but it was a passageway
从人族帝国通往这里
to get to this place from the Terran Empire.
从你们宇宙的新月星云穿出
Comes out through your Crescent Nebula.
至少目前还是鲜有人知的
Few know about it. For now.
但它四小时后会重新开放
But it'll open again in four hours.
那本来是我要去见买家的时间
That's when I was supposed to be meeting my buyer.
你知道那武器的威力吗
Are you aware of what that weapon does?
人族帝国已经耗尽了所有资源
The Terran Empire's burned through its resources.
饥荒肆虐 饿殍遍地
There's famine.
整个生态系统正在崩溃
Entire ecologies are collapsing.
它们需要寻找新的领土
They need to find a new territory
进行征服和压榨
to conquer and strip-mine.
当他们意识到他们的超级武器不见了
When they realize that their superweapon is gone,
他们一定会找到那条通道
they're gonna find that passageway--
你知道他们会的 然后来到这里
you know they will-- and they'll come
烧杀抢掠每一寸领土 再奴役余生
and they'll burn everything they touch and enslave the rest,
您的帝国向来如此 陛下
because that's what the Empire does, Majesty.
他们学您学到了精髓
They learned well from you.
还有谁想要它？
Who else wants it?
我真的不知道
I-I don't know, man.
我收到了一个报价 钱是真的
I got an offer. The money was real.
有人偷走了我们的天赐之物
Someone stole the Godsend from us.
究竟是谁
Who was he?
我真不清楚
No idea.
无论是谁闯入我的套间 偷走了那件武器
Whoever broke into my room, whoever stole that weapon,
知道这些事的人
they know what they know
肯定是从你们其中之一得来的
because they learned it from one of you.
紧急传送
Emergency transporter.
这下好了
Well, this is great.
更棒了
Oh, even better.
那是我们的船吗 船炸了吗
Is that... is that the ship? Is the ship gone?
我还挺喜欢那艘船的
I liked that ship.
什么情况
What happened?
有人搞破坏
Sabotage.
什么
What?
偷走天赐之物的人有一个同伙
Whoever stole the Godsend had a partner.
就在我们几个之中
It was someone here.
这意味着我们中的一个是内鬼
Which means one of us is a mole.
可能是你
Could be you.
原话奉还
要是我的话 我早把你们都杀了
If it were me, I would have murdered all of you already.
大哥 你是了解我的
Look, boss, if there's a mole,
绝对不可能是我
you know it's not me.
虽然这话听起来也就很像内奸说的 我也不确定
I mean, that sounds pretty moley to me. I don't know.
我们合作过差不多十次了
We've been on like ten ops together.
是没错 但我连你长什么样都不知道
Yeah, and I still don't even know what you look like, do I?
没人知道查莫人长什么样子
No one knows what a Chameloid looks like.
你可以变成任何你想变的样子
You might change into anything you want.
那法兹呢
What about Fuzz, huh?
他的体型与其他人都不在一个尺度上
He exists on a whole other scale than anybody else.
转移话题是吗
Mm, deflecting?
我的妻子即将产下我们的第一窝卵囊
My wife is about to lay our first litter of egg sacs.
而且我还有19万只幼崽正在路上
No, I have 190,000 hatchlings on the way...
- 我希望他们活下去  - 那你听着
- and I want them to live.  - Well, look,
你可以在我们中的任何人找到动机
you could find a motive for any of us.
也可能是你们中任何两个的组合
Or it could be a combination of any of you.
你看 就像泽弗和法兹或者其他
You know, like-like Zeph and-and Fuzz or...
你还漏掉了梅尔
You are spinning out without Melle.
你根本没法做出判断
You cannot land on a choice.
也许是你想给我灌输这个观点
Maybe you're putting that in my head
因为你才是内鬼
because you're the mole.
又会不会是加勒特 她可是新来的
Huh? How about Garrett? She's new.
她才不在乎我们
She doesn't care about us.
我可是星际舰队的军官
I'm Starfleet.
还有没有人像我一样感受到一阵英雄主义的风
Anyone else feel that heroic breeze right there
弄乱了她的斗篷?
ruffling her cape?
听我讲 那边有一艘旧船
Okay, there's an old ship out there,
一艘旧垃圾驳船
an old garbage scow.
我发现它的时候你们还在
Yeah, I found it when you were up there
审问那个金属脑袋
interrogating metal head.
肯定已经很多年没人驾驶过它了
Must be years since anyone flew it,
但我认为我们可以修复它
but I think we can work with it
开着它去追捕拿走天赐之物的人
to go after whoever took the Godsend.
我没那么讨厌你了
I dislike you less.
如果我想有人喜欢我 我就会养一只狗
If I wanted someone to like me, I'd get a dog.
我喜欢秩序
I like order.
我喜欢预测和结论
I like prediction and conclusion.
那你可来错队伍了
Then you're on the wrong team
因为我们这还没揪出内鬼
because we've got mole,
被困在一颗荒无人烟的星球
stranded on a dead planet,
无法联络外界
no communication with the outside,
而且不到四个小时之后人族将得到天赐之物
and less than four hours before the Terrans get the Godsend
并在银河系的任意一处使用它
and use it anywhere in the galaxy.
说起来
Speaking of which,
小夸 天线阵列怎么样了
Quas, what about the antenna array?
这个嘛
Uh, well...
这玩意已经过时几十年了
Well, it's a couple decades out of date.
我们修复它 把目前的情况告知31区
We get it up and running, then we tell 31 what's coming.
我们齐心协力
We work together.
每个人都不要离开彼此的视线
Everyone stays in sight.
好
Yeah.
我盯着呢
Just...
干活吧
Let's go.
修好怕是没那么简单了
Well, there goes that idea.
我们的小内鬼真的很忙
Our little mole has been really busy.
扯断了所有线路
Ripped up all the wiring.
分两个队 我会带一个进入树林
Two teams. I'll lead one into the woods.
我带三个人进树林
I'll lead one into the woods.
试试看能不能修好那艘小艇
Three to see if we can salvage that scow.
你和其他人一起留在这里
You stay here with the others
并尝试修复天线阵列
and try and fix the antenna array.
怎么轮到她来发号施令了
Why is she giving us orders now?
因为是我让的
Because I'm letting her
而且她十有八九不是内奸
and I'm pretty certain she's not the mole.
你可不会把赌注押在「十有八九」的身上吧
You wouldn't bet on a horse named Pretty Certain.
小夸、法兹 你们马上和乔久一起去船
Quas, Fuzz, you get to the scow right away with Georgiou.
泽弗和加勒特 你们跟我待在这
Zeph and Garrett, you stay here with me.
我们会搞定天线阵列的
We'll take care of the antenna array.
请解释一下
Uh, I'm sorry.
我是应该出去
I'm supposed to go out into the woods
和两个想杀我的人一起进入树林吗
with two people who want to kill me?
保持在彼此的视线之内 别死了就行
Just stay in sight of each other and don't get dead.
好吗
Okay?
真是多谢了 头儿
Yep, thanks, Cap.
我得说 50%的几率他们中的一个想杀我
I mean, just fifty-fifty shot one of them wants to kill me,
还有25%的几率
and then 25%...
别贫嘴了小夸 快出发
Quas, just get your ass out there.
我也爱你 头儿
I love you, too, Cap.
行了行了
All righty.
遵命
Aye, aye.
这艘旧船上的内部电路
The internal circuitry on this old scow
状态还不错
is still in decent shape.
我看这些应该都还能用
Everything I'm seeing should work.
所以我们正在追的东西 天赐之物
So this thing we're chasing, the Godsend,
你的工程师 他们安装保险没有?
your engineers, did they install a fail-safe?
可以远程解除它吗
Can we disable it remotely?
没有这种保险
There is no fail-safe.
我不会允许的
I wouldn't allow it.
不愧是你
How very on-brand for you.
可以再问你一个问题吗
Can I ask you one more question?
真的最后一个问题了
I'm just gonna ask you one more question.
既然你主导了天赐之物的制造
So you brought the Godsend into the world
目的就是抹杀万亿条生命
to vaporize quadrillions of lives.
就从没想过这有点
Never thought that was a little,
太心狠手辣了吗
you know, much?
我早已下令销毁它
I ordered it destroyed.
但有人把它藏起来了
And someone hid it.
你自己的人背叛了你
Your own people betrayed you.
反正 你们的企业文化都烂到到不可救药了
Well, your corporate culture was straight-up shit.
而且你还是没回答我的问题
And you didn't answer my question.
渐进线圈不见了
The asymptote coil is gone.
肯定是有人为了铽元素把它拆走了
Someone must have scavenged it for the terbium.
那再找一个 这个东西应该能飞
Well, find another one, this thing should fly.
也许货舱就有
Maybe the cargo hull.
别去
Huh. Oh, no, no.
每个人都待在一起 好吗
Everyone stays together, all right?
降低你杀死我们的可能性
Limits the possibilities of you killing us.
我们去货舱吧
Let's go to the cargo hold, please.
你不来吗
Aren't you coming?
当然 我可太高兴了
Yes. I couldn't be more excited.
当然 我可以下去帮你
Yeah, I could help you down there, of course,
但考虑到 控制我们的行动
but considering how, you know, control
是你整个身份的核心
is central to your entire identity
而我本来就不太能接受这种事
and the fact that I'm just not good at it,
所以我就站在这里
I'm just gonna stand here
- 为了我们的关系 什么也不做了 - 那你还真热心呢
- and honor our relationship by doing absolutely nothing. - Helpful.
这叫做彻底的自我接纳
It's called radical self-acceptance.
- 那你真是进步了 - 谢谢夸奖
- Evolved of you. - Well, thank you.
所以说 你能修好它吗？
So, can you fix it?
我甚至不确定它是否坏了
I'm not even sure it's broken.
它只是缺了个零件
It's just missing a part.
看这里 这些被乱扯的线路看着很严重
Look, this-this torn wiring looks dramatic,
但这设备本身就有冗余设计
but this equipment has redundancy built in.
有一个简单的解决办法
There's an easy work-around.
唯一问题是 有人取出了θ节点
Except somebody ripped out the theta junction.
除此之外 这个东西应该可以用
Other than that, this thing should work.
好吧 也许我们的内鬼拿走了它
Okay, well, maybe our mole has it.
加勒特?
Garrett?
咋了
Yeah.
泽弗
Zeph.
泽弗去哪了
Where is Zeph?
泽弗 收到请回复
Zeph, come in.
泽弗 你能听到吗
Zeph, do you copy?
泽弗
Zeph.
加勒特 是你做的吗
Garrett, was that you?
加勒特 刚刚那是什么情况
Garrett, what the hell was that?
有人刚激活了天线阵列
Someone just activated the antenna array.
该死
Damn it.
具体情况如何
What's happening?
加勒特 情况简报
Garrett, sitrep.
越来越棒了
This is going to be good.
上尉 收到请回复 完毕
Lieutenant, do you copy? Over.
安全
Clear.
这里什么都没有
Nothing here.
怎么会有人用这个来发出信号呢
How could someone have used this to send out a signal?
不可能 它少了一个部件
Impossible. It's missing a part.
有人把它打成了筛子
And someone shot it to hell.
我听到有人在跑
I heard someone running.
泽弗一定是把θ节点放回去了
Zeph must have put the theta junction back in.
使用完毕后 射击毁掉了阵列
Then shot it after he used the array.
所以他肯定是在擅离职守后绕回来的
So he must have circled back after he went AWOL.
泽弗来这个星球来阻碍我们
Zeph came down to this planet to sabotage us.
现在我们被困住了
And now that we're stranded,
他用阵列给同谋发了信息
he sent a message to whoever he's working with.
他会潜伏直到撤离的船抵达
And he'll lay low until his ride gets here,
然后溜之大吉
and then he's long gone.
那我们得先找到他
Then we need to find him first.
观察者 能收到吗
Observer, do you copy?
拜托 突袭者一号 我什么时候收不到了
Please, Raider One, when do I not copy?
真好笑 情况如何
That's funny. Status?
我检测到了不少干扰
I'm picking up a lot of interference,
但三录仪显示 泽弗的生命信号
but the tricorder shows Zeph's biosignature
就在这个区域 完毕
was just in this sector. Over.
收到 保持低调 保持队形
Copy. Stay low and tight, people.
你曾效力的那个军阀 吉里
The warlord you served, Giri,
她后来怎样了
what happened to her?
她死了 死于生前最爱的事
She died like she lived.
你知道我说的什么
By that, you know what I mean.
她很幸运
She was lucky.
没染上良心这种东西
She wasn't infected with a conscience.
染上?
Infected?
是啊
Yeah.
怪物就只能是个怪物
A monster can only be a monster.
一个会悔恨的怪物是没用的
A monster with regrets is useless.
嗯 所以这就是你
Mm. So that's why you were hiding
躲在那个偏远酒吧的原因
in a bar at the ass end of nowhere.
也许这就是你和31区的人合作的原因
Maybe it's why you're working with 31.
把自己的前科抹干净
To wipe your slate clean.
像我们这样的人总是要付出代价的
There's always a price to pay for people like us.
如果你不同意 你就不会在这里
You wouldn't be here if you didn't agree.
所以这就是你选择我的原因
Oh, so that's why you chose me.
你认为我是一个有足够感情的怪物
You think I'm a monster who feels enough
可以被控制
to be controlled
也还能做那些脏活
but still do the real dirty work.
不 我认为你想找回天赐之物
No, I think you want the Godsend back
因为你知道这是你救赎自己的唯一机会
because you know it's your one chance to redeem yourself
为你所做的一切赎罪
for all the shit you've done.
我想找回它 只因为它本就属于我
I want the Godsend back because it's mine.
泽弗的外骨骼装甲正在渗漏
Ah. Zeph's exoskeleton is leaking.
漏液更多了
Yep, more.
这边
This way.
闪
Blip,
夹
Clip,
抓
Grip,
脊灰
Polio,
流感
Influensina,
牛痘
Cowpox...
你在念什么呢
What are you saying?
我正在背诵我即将孵化的幼崽的名字
I'm reciting the names of me hatchlings.
既然你们中的一个要谋杀我
Since one of you is going to murder me,
我应该是见不到他们了
I'm never gonna meet them,
但至少我可以这样纪念他们
but at least I can honor them
一个接一个
one by one.
旅行
Trip,
旅行二世
Trip 2,
扁桃体炎
Tonsilyitis,
克里米亚-刚果出血热
Crimean-Congo Hemorrhagic Fever...
你要哭着念完19万孩子的名字吗
Are you gonna sob out 190,000 names?
你怎么能这么冷漠 如此无情
How can you be so cold and insensitive?
他有可能记录下了发生的一切吗
Might he have recorded what happened?
当然
Sure.
只是这段视频很可能和他一起被谋杀了
Except the footage was probably murdered along with him.
我们可以将三录仪连接到外骨骼装甲上
We could connect one of the tricorders to his suit.
就算没剩多少数据
Whatever data is left,
凶手也昭然若揭了
we'll know who did this.
说得好像我们都是嫌疑人一样
You say that like we're all suspects.
并不是 好吗
We're not. All right?
那时候我 法兹和乔久都在那艘船里
Fuzz, me and her were in the scow when all this happened--
每个人都在彼此的视线范围内
everyone in sight of everyone else.
没一个人乱跑 没错吧
And nobody went anywhere, right?
对啊
Right.
这不是泽弗的
Oh, this is not Zeph's.
深褐色头发 25厘米
Brunette. 25 centimeters.
这太疯狂了
This is insane.
别再坐立不安了
Stop fidgeting.
我已经和泽弗近距离接触了一周了
I've been in close quarters with Zeph for a week.
行 所以你喜欢机甲什么的
Okay, so you're into mecha boom-boom.
很多人类都是 不必害羞
Lots of humans are. No shame.
检测到血液
呃 那不可能啊
Well, that's impossible.
加勒特上尉
Lieutenant Garrett,
痕迹匹配
为什么你的指甲缝里会有泽弗的血
why is Zeph's blood underneath your fingernails?
加勒特上尉
Lieutenant Garrett,
在泽弗的尸体上发现了你的证据
evidence from you was found on Zeph's body,
泽弗尸体上的证据也在你身上发现了
and evidence from Zeph's body was found on you.
不像星际舰队的作风啊
Not very Starfleet.
我问心无愧
Oh, I am very Starfleet.
你清楚凶手并不是我
And you know I didn't do this.
你只是害怕任何有道德准则的人
You are just terrified of anyone with a moral compass.
但在那颗纯洁的小心灵的深处
And deep down in that pure little heart,
你其实是个混乱小妖精 没错吧
you're actually a chaos goblin, aren't you?
- 我知道你是这样的 小天使  - 别这么叫我
- I know you have it in you, angel. - Don't call me that.
星际舰队发现了这样的你
Starfleet sniffed you out
把你放在了最能发挥你作用的地方
and put you in a place where you'd be most useful.
31区正是为那些打破规则
Section 31 is just the place for officers
却又从未真正越界的军官准备的地方
who bend the rules, never quite break them until they do.
而你 正好适合这里
And you fit right in here.
你想怎么折磨我都可以
You can torture me all you want.
但我坚持自己没杀过人
You will never make me a murderer.
住手
No.
我们拿到录像了
We've got footage!
住手
Stop!
快住手
这是我的装甲
This is my suit.
我即是装甲！
I am the suit!
装甲就是我！
The suit is me!
等一下
One second.
我们是你的朋友
We were your friends.
曾是你的朋友
你杀不了我
You can't kill me.
泽弗 别
Zeph, no.
你不能
You can't kill...
泽弗是自杀的?
Zeph killed himself?
他为什么要这么做
Why would he do that?
抱歉让您失望了 陛下
Sorry to disappoint you, Your Majesty.
这一切根本说不通
Look, none of this is making any sense.
是啊 非常之不合理
No, none of it makes a lick of sense.
他为什么要这样做呢
Why would he do this?
给我几分钟时间
Give me a couple minutes to...
我们没时间了
We don't have minutes.
那就几秒钟行了没
Well, then give me a couple seconds, then.
可能是你
Could be you.
原话奉还
但我连你长什么样都不知道
And I still don't even know what you look like.
你可以变成任何你想变的样子
You could change into anything you want.
她是新来的 她才不在乎我们
She's new. She doesn't care about us.
我可是星际舰队的军官
I'm Starfleet.
当你在说我这套装甲的时候
When you are talking about the suit,
就是在说我
you're talking about Zeph.
这可不是法兹
This isn't Fuzz.
这个瓦肯外表不过是台机器
The Vulcan's just a machine, you know.
我在里面呢
I'm inside.
这是身材羞辱
Scale-shamer!
你绝对想不到我能进入多小的地方
You wouldn't believe the tiny spots I can get into.
比如 身体改造组件的内部空间
For example, the inner workings of body modifications.
当时他启用了自动驾驶
There's an autopilot.
这是唯一合理的解释
That's the only thing that makes sense.
你给瓦肯机器设定了自动驾驶程序
You set the Vulcan machine on autopilot.
所以当时它的反应才那么古怪
That's why its responses were so strange.
你来不来
Aren't you coming?
当然
Yes.
你钻进了泽弗的外骨骼装甲
You flew into Zeph's exoskeleton.
你钻进去之后
And once you were inside...
有人把西塔接口拆掉了
Somebody ripped out  the theta junction.
加勒特 泽弗去哪了
Garrett, where's Zeph?
然后你控制了泽弗的装甲
Then you took control of Zeph's suit.
当别人在找他的时候
While the others were out looking for him,
你控制他溜回了通讯阵列
you made him sneak back into the antenna array
然后发送了那些信息
and send those messages.
不要这么做
Don't do this to them!
我们是你的朋友啊
We were your friends.
然后你销毁了所有证据
Then you destroyed the evidence.
还杀掉了泽弗
And you killed Zeph.
然后你再把这一切嫁祸给加勒特
And then you planted the evidence on Garrett here.
举起手来 法兹
Hands up, Fuzz.
真是倒了血霉了
Oh, shite and ever shite.
阿洛克 你不会真的要信她的鬼话吧
You're honestly gonna believe what she says, Alok?
夸西 我们一起经历了这么多 你也信她的话吗
Quasi, after everything we've been through?
我能先说一句吗
C-Can I just say one thing first?
泽弗的外骨骼我还控制着呢
I'm still hacked into Zeph's exoskeleton.
喂
Come on!
说好的「不抛弃任何人」呢
What happened to "no crew member left behind"?
快一点啊
Come on, come on!
靠近他们
Get us closer.
接住你了
I got you. I got you.
还好有我
Nice and easy.
该死
Damn.
你很关注黑市的动向 没错吧
You keep tabs on the black market, hmm?
你就是在那听说天赐之物的消息的
And that's where you heard about the Godsend.
你在乎这些干什么
Why do you care?
家人你都下得去手
You killed your family.
再多点人算什么呢
What's a few billion more people, huh?
天赐之物在哪 你的同谋是谁
Where is it? And who are you working with?
你登上了皇位
You took your crown
他们却痛苦地死在你的脚边
while they died in agony not ten feet away.
你奴役了你唯一的朋友
You condemned your only friend to slavery,
居然还有脸在最后一刻给他一些怜悯?
and then you had the balls to offer him kindness at the end?
你怎么会知道的
How could you know that?
你终于发现了
Glad you're catching on.
他把你耍了 女皇陛下
He played you, Emperor.
桑还活着
San's alive.
不可能
It's not possible.
绝对不可能 到底怎么回事
That's not possible. How?
他训练出了对毒药的抗药性
He built up an immunity from that poison, you know.
每次只多服用很小的剂量
Teeny tiny doses over time.
看样子是小混蛋又赢了一次
Once again, small shite for the win, mama.
他在哪
Where is he?!
期待他的精彩表演吧
He's gonna put on quite the show.
你制造了天赐之物
You built the Godsend.
你制造了一个怪物
You made this monster.
全是因为你
This is all you.
小心点可以吗
Be careful, all right?
我让你小心点
I said be careful.
我还得用它活动呢
I have to get around in that.
你都能买得起一百多具身体了 还在乎这一具
You can afford a hundred of them now.
太好了
Oh, great.
这个能用不就行了
I'd settle for one that works.
所以就是这个
So that's it?
无敌的天赐之物
The almighty Godsend.
等你做上皇帝了
When you're emperor,
能不能给它换个没那么奇怪的名字
maybe start by naming it something less confusing.
离子风暴会聚倒计时
跨越两个宇宙的通道打开时
Once that passageway opens up,
他会联系人族 他们会从中进入
he contacts the Terrans, they come through.
然后他们会在此引爆
They're detonating it here.
他就会成为帝国的新宠
And he'd be the darling of the Empire.
发生这样的灾难 星联就会陷入混乱
So he throws the Federation into chaos...
星际舰队自顾不暇
Starfleet will start scrambling.
入侵的完美时机
Perfect time to invade.
你创造了它
You gave birth to this thing.
我们要如何阻止
How do we stop it?
没办法
We don't.
我们被困在这 追不上他
We're trapped here, so we can't follow him.
通讯天线坏了 我们也无法警告任何人
The antenna's destroyed, so we can't warn anybody.
胡扯
That is bullshit.
你肯定有更好的办法
You can do better than that.
我做不到
I can't.
天赐之物就像我自己
The Godsend is me.
我唯一无法战胜的就是自己
I'm the only one I could never defeat.
过去总是缠着你不放
The past always catches up with you.
不是吗
Right?
但并不意味着它总能赢
Doesn't mean it always wins.
每个安全屋都有备用计划
Every safe house, I have a backup plan.
把那艘垃圾船修好
We'll get that scow running.
老大 那家伙飞不起来的
Boss, the scow won't fly.
没有渐进线圈就不可能
Not without an asymptote coil.
我们有一个
We have one.
我们必须追上桑
We'll catch up with San.
我们要阻止他联系人族帝国
We'll make sure he can't contact the Terrans.
你早把线圈拆出来了
You ripped out the coil.
有内奸在 我可没法什么都说出来
Couldn't tell you while a mole was still running around.
你个混蛋
Asshole.
小夸 去帮她一下
Okay, Quas, give her a rip.
还是只有一下反应
Still just one pulse.
来活了 朋友们
And we're in business.
我们只有不到三十分钟时间
Okay, team, we have less than 30 minutes.
小夸 设定航线前往新月星云
Quas, set a course for the Crescent Nebula.
路上将会非常颠簸
All right, this is gonna be bumpy and bad.
我推测桑的星舰会有武器
I'm assuming San's ship will be armed.
废话 人族帝国能有不武装的星舰吗
Yeah, every Terran ship's armed.
对方有质子加农炮 鱼雷
He'll have proton cannons, torpedoes,
而我们只有一堆垃圾
and we are a garbage barge.
有啥好笑的
Why are you laughing?
因为我想不出来还有什么更糟的情况了
Because I can't imagine things getting much worse.
出发
Let's go.
所以 这艘船会在自身周围制造牵引力场
So, this thing flies around in the middle of a tractor field.
人们向太空里面扔垃圾
People jettison their garbage into space,
然后这种驳船会拖着垃圾和力场
and the scow flies around and drags the trash
一起飞行
along with the field.
牵引力场里塞满垃圾之后
Once the tractor field is full,
就会一起把垃圾甩进星云里
it dumps the trash in the Nebula
让垃圾在辐射里自行分解
where it disintegrates in the radiation.
我就是想确认一下
I just want to be clear.
你是说我们最有可能用的上的武器
You're saying that our best potential weapon is
是用来拖垃圾的牵引光束吗
a beam for collecting garbage?
没错
Yes.
那太棒了
Great.
提醒下 你在那指手画脚帮不上一点忙
Hey, being judgy never helped anything.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
轮机室
Engineering.
如果那是我们唯一的武器
If that's our only weapon,
我要把所有的能量都导入那里
I'll redirect all power to the tractor beams.
这计划确实不错呢
That's actually a good plan.
（加密传讯3）
（跨越宇宙的通道）
我们就位了
We're in position.
通道很快就会打开
The passageway will open soon.
你知道我在这一切结束后想干什么吗
Do you know what I want when this is all over?
这么大的一块空域
Just a big space, you know,
我要和我的小家伙们到处乱飞
for me hatchlings to tunnel and fly around and...
那你呢
What do you want?
我要菲利帕乔久永远沉沦于她的失败之中
I want Philippa Georgiou to marinate in her own defeat.
我明白你们之间是那种
I get you guys are all
「永恒宿敌 性感的邪恶张力」之类的关系
"eternal nemesis, sexy evil tension" and stuff, but...
警报
Alert.
有飞船靠近
Incoming vessel.
检测到碰撞航线
Collision trajectory detected.
她确实能把那玩意飞起来
Of course she got it off the ground.
我建议用鱼雷解决他们
I say we should use the torpedoes.
对方发现我们了
They've picked us up.
光子鱼雷来袭
Photon torpedo incoming.
击中倒计时
Impact in five, four...
是时候进行规避机动了吧
Really want to take evasive action right now!
小夸 维持航线 护盾强度设置到最大
Quas, hold the course. Put everything in our shields.
她为什么不改变航线呢
Why isn't she changing course?
我看起来像是算命师吗
Do I look like a fortune teller?
我们有足够的能量使用牵引光束锁定他们吗
Do we have enough juice to drag them with the tractor beam yet?
有 但我们没法再承受鱼雷的直接命中了
Yeah, but we can't take another direct hit.
鱼雷即将命中 五 四 三
Incoming torpedo in five, four...
先维持航线 我们马上就位了
Keep it steady. We're almost there...
闪避
Now.
警告 导航控制功能失效
Alert. Navigation control suspended.
他们在干什么 想拽死我们吗
What are they gonna do, drag us to death?
她在阻止我和帝国取得联系
She's trying to stop me from reaching the Empire.
怎么样 大家没事吧
How's everybody feeling about this?
这是唯一的办法了
It's the only way.
这办法有用
This can work.
辐射会削减他们的护盾
The radiation will wear down their shields.
是啊 但是辐射也会影响我们
Yeah, the thing is, the radiation hits us, too.
目标锁定系统失效
Target lock malfunction.
鱼雷无法锁定目标 加农炮也离线了
I can't get torpedo lock. Cannons offline.
桑?
San?
桑
San.
桑!
San!
辐射已达致命水平
Radiation levels critical.
护盾失效 重复 护盾失效了
Shields are down. I repeat, shields are down!
他的呢
And San's?
还剩12% 仍在迅速下降
His are at 12% and falling fast.
等离子辐射来袭
Plasma incoming!
如果我们被卷入这样的爆炸里
We get caught with a burst like that,
我们就完了
and we're done.
这就是混乱 加勒特
This is chaos, Garrett.
你喜欢混乱没错吧
You know you love it, hmm?
直面它 接纳它 享受混乱
Maybe let it in, make out with it a little.
这就是星际舰队派你到此的原因
It's why Starfleet put you here.
混乱就像是我的炮友
Chaos is my friend with benefits.
就是这样 越混乱越好
Yeah, Garrett, let's get messy.
怎么样
Hmm?
当然
Okay.
加油 小夸 你能行的
You got this, Quas.
没问题
Uh-huh.
准备好了吗
You ready?
桑的护盾只有4%了
San's shields are at four percent.
最后2%
Two now.
他的护盾已失效
His shields are down.
可以出发了
Good to go.
菲利帕
Philippa!
我们这次
This contest only ends
不死不休
when one of us is dead!
引爆程序已启动
Detonation sequence activating.
听好了 我们纳米人
See, the Nanokins,
不需要星际联邦
we don't need the Federation.
向来如此
We never have.
早在你们这些庞然大物发现我们之前我们就在统治了
We ruled before you behemoths found us,
在你们死后 我们会再次统治
and we will rule again after you're gone.
猜猜谁会在待会的大爆炸中存活下来
Guess who survives very large explosions.
是我们纳米人
Very small things.
好了 我先失陪了
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我得让船脱离牵引光束
I need to cut our ship loose.
如果你的朋友在这个过程里死了那真是抱歉
Sorry if your friends die in the process.
不 我在开玩笑
No, I'm joking.
我等不及要杀死他们了
I can't wait to kill them.
再见了 你个巨大狗屎
So long, you big lumps of shite!
谁在驾驶那艘飞船
Who's flying that?
根据传感器 上面有一个微型生命
Uh, according to the sensors, one tiny life-form on board,
它在朝我们飞来
and it's heading right for us.
导弹锁定
Plot missile lock.
我们只有垃圾 明白吗 只有垃圾
We have trash, all right? Just trash.
但为一体
But one.
桑
San.
等待确认生物签名
Awaiting biosignature confirmation.
我追踪到法兹的穿梭艇了
I've got Fuzz's shuttle.
他要回到桑的船上
He's heading back to San's ship.
我们只能勉强跟上
We're barely keeping up.
跟住他
Stay on him.
提醒下 我们没有任何武器
Uh, we don't have any weapons.
我们有一个满载垃圾的货舱
We have a payload bay full of trash.
不要跟丢那个穿梭艇
Do not lose that shuttle.
好吧
Okay.
我曾经什么都不是
I was nothing!
那个男孩软弱无力
That boy was soft, weak.
但在你脚下服侍的这些年教出了现在的我
But all those years under your heel taught me who I am now.
帝国舰队将会穿过通道过来
The Empire's coming through that portal.
我的帝国
My Empire!
我们将统治这个宇宙
And we will reign over this universe
用公正又仁慈的手段 不像你
with righteous mercy, not like you!
从来不会有仁慈的独裁者 桑
There are no benevolent dictators, San.
这是你教会我的
You taught me that.
我们还能回头
We can come back from this.
我们可以重新开始
We can start over.
我爱混乱
Oh, I love chaos.
混乱是我的菜
Chaos is my jam.
我爱混乱
I love chaos.
加勒特 你在那里边干啥呢
Garrett, what the hell are you doing down there?
夸西 我是个训练有素的星际舰队军官
Quasi, I am a trained Starfleet officer
我也非常希望活得到能当上舰长的那一天
who fully intends on living long enough to be captain one day.
你得相信我 好吗
You got to trust me, okay?
你好呀
Hi there.
真高兴你找到了我
I'm so glad you found me.
你刚刚说啥了
What'd you just say?
是玩具说的
It's a toy.
看起来它来自一个德鲁姆行星
Looks like it came from a Droom planet.
来一起找点乐子怎么样
Shall we do something fun together?
你还好吗 星际舰队女士
You okay down there, Starfleet?
哦 拜托 拜托 拜托 太好了
Oh, come on, come on, come on, come on. Yes.
我们不允许德鲁姆科技进入联邦
Oh, we do not let Droom tech into the Federation
因为他们用特瑞金作为电源
because they use Terrenium as a power source.
你是准备炸飞我们吗
Oh, you're gonna blow us up, aren't you?
你最好希望这艘船的船体
You better hope that this ship's hull
用特莫矿加固过
is reinforced with Tomohite.
我是一名科学官
I am a science officer.
而科学就是受控的混乱
And science is just controlled chaos.
混乱 混乱 混乱
Whoa, chaos, chaos!
得了吧
Ah, come on.
起来 你个愚蠢的机器人
Get up, you stupid robot.
不 不
No. No.
不
No!
维持位置在法兹的飞船前
Stay in front of Fuzz's ship
这样才能打开舱门往上倒垃圾
so we can open the payload bay.
呃 好
Uh, yeah.
我正想说呢
About that.
是这样
Uh, thing is...
夸西 马上就要发生非常大的爆炸
Quasi, there's about to be a very large explosion.
这个控制台的语言我看不懂
This console's in a language I don't know.
我能破译其中一些
I can decipher some of it.
我只需要把它分解成语素
I just have to break it down to morphemes
然后 你知道
and, you know...
大爆炸要来了啊
Large explosion impending.
这两个按钮都有可能打开货舱
Either of these two buttons could open the cargo bay.
好啊 那就都按了
Okay, so push them both.
这两个按钮也都有可能
Either of these two buttons could also
启动自毁程序
initiate a self-destruct protocol.
反正怎样都是爆炸呗
We're gonna blow up anyway.
嗯哼
Uh-huh
夸西 夸西 看着我
Quasi. Quasi, look at me.
你只需要做个决定
You just need to make a call.
你知道该做什么
You know what to do.
好
Okay.
我们可以做永远的好朋友
We can be friends forever...
你想听点有趣的事吗
Do you want to hear something funny?
我在自动驾驶状态
I'm on autopilot.
什么鬼
What the hell?
我们都要死了
We're all gonna die.
挥发性物质警告
不
No!
能和你在一起真是太好了
It's wonderful just to be with you.
好
Yes!
死吧
Die now.
去告诉你的家人你变成了什么样
Go tell your family how much you've changed.
桑
San.
不
No.
桑
San.
这不是我想要的结局
This is not what I want.
别死
Please.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
桑
San.
对不起
I'm sorry.
真的对不起
I'm so sorry.
你 你是对的
You-you-you were right.
我仍然需要你
I still needed you.
我一直需要
I always needed...
让我明白我是谁 即便是现在
To show me who I am, even now.
现在
Now.
我的皇帝
M-M... My emperor.
我的挚爱
My love.
不
No.
我们双生一体
We are one.
直到永远
Forever.
离子风暴即将会聚
Ion storm convergence imminent.
跨越通道正在打开
Passageway is opening.
生物签名已确认
Biosignature confirmed.
六十秒后引爆
Detonation in 60 seconds.
计算机 目标锁定跨越通道
Computer, target lock on the passageway.
目标锁定已确认
Target lock confirmed.
如果你能回到过去
If you could go back,
回到跪在吉里面前那时
and you were kneeling in front of Giri,
你会杀了她吗
would you kill her?
你愿意永远结束所有的痛苦和硝烟
Would you put a stop to all the suffering and smoke forever,
就算这意味着你必须死去
even if it meant that you had to die?
我会的
Yes.
那么我很高兴认识了你 阿洛克·萨哈
Then I'm glad I knew you, Alok Sahar.
三十秒后引爆
Detonation in 30 seconds.
通道已打开
Passageway is open.
传感器显示他们启动了脉冲引擎
Sensors show they've activated impulse engines.
什么
What?
没错
Yeah.
你得把他们传送回来
You need to transport them back.
-好的  -快点
- Yeah. Okay. - Now.
好的 好的
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
离子风暴在干扰我们
The storm's interfering.
我无法锁定他们
I can't lock on to them.
十秒后引爆
Detonation in ten seconds.
快点 快点
Come on. Come on!
他们要没时间了
They're running out of time.
我在努力
I'm trying.
五秒后引爆
Detonation in five,
四
four,
三
three,
二
two,
一
one.
加勒特上尉
Lieutenant Garrett?
瑞秋?
Rachel?
你还好吗
You all right?
-我还好  -缓过来了吗
- I'm okay. - Hmm? You here?
看来没事
All right.
嗯 你还活着
Yeah. You're alive.
是啊 夸西把我们救出来了
Yeah, Quasi got us out.
-好了 好了 起来吧  -谢谢
- There we go. There we are. - Thank you.
你做到了
Oh, you did it.
我们赢了
Oh, we won.
成熟一点
Oh. Grow up.
这么活泼让我有点恶心
Perkiness is disgusting.
好吧
Yeah.
我知道了
I hear you.
就这样了
It's happening.
通道在坍塌
The passageway's collapsing.
（最终传讯 三个地球周之后）
原来你在这
There she is.
你的汇报如何
How was your debrief?
够好的了
Oh, could've been worse.
他们给我发了邀请
They made me an offer.
然后呢
And?
我还在考虑
I'm sitting on it.
你呢
You?
还行 嗯
Meh. Hmm.
你觉得你能用这招
And how long did you think
骗过我几次 嗯
you could fool me with this, hmm?
哪里暴露了
What gave it away?
我看着你时你还会紧张
You still get nervous when I look at you.
你好啊 队长
Oh. Hey, C-Cap.
放过那个可怜的家伙吧
Leave that poor man alone.
维吉尔
Virgil.
给我的朋友上轮好酒
A round of elixirs for my friends.
没问题 杜·弗朗克女士
Pleasure, Madame du Franc.
加勒特上尉
Lieutenant Garrett.
他们放你下船了
They let you off the ship.
实际上 现在是加勒特少校了
It's actually Lieutenant Commander Garrett now.
谢谢你们
Thank you very much.
如果这个小队要成为常驻的
And if this unit is gonna be a permanent detail,
那你们绝对需要有人监督
then you all definitely need oversight.
我随时都可能杀掉你们所有人
I may slaughter you all at any moment.
算是个雷点吗
Is that a deal-breaker?
-不算吧 -无所谓啊
- Nah. - Whatevs.
反正你也不需要什么理由
It's not like you need a reason anyway.
还真是 你就是个坏女人
It's true. You're a bad bitch.
带着死亡凝视
With the stare of death.
哦 我们懂
Oh, we get it.
你是个可怕的冷血杀手
You're a terrifying, soulless murderer
我们永远也不能真心相信你
who we can never truly trust.
我真为咱们感到高兴啊
I love that for us.
总有人得活跃气氛
Somebody's got to keep things lively.
说得好
Touché.
是啊 说得好
Yes, touché.
你说得对
You make a point.
敬我们
To us.
里面没放毒吧
This isn't poison, is it?
现在你把我们都叫过来了
And now that you have us all here,
下一步是什么
what next?
也不全在
Well, not quite all.
女士们先生们 看舞台左侧
Ladies and gent, stage left.
你一定在开玩笑吧
You got to be kidding me.
哦 我不是法兹
Oh, I'm not Fuzz.
31区从黑市上
Section 31 bought
买了两个这种运输工具
two of these conveyances on the black market.
我叫薇丝 是他的妻子
Name's Wisp. I'm his wife.
我来是为了抓到那个
And I'm here for when we catch up with
满嘴扯谎 两面三刀的混蛋
that lying, double-dealing son of a bitch.
呃 我们可是把他的船炸了的 女士
Uh, well, we blew up his ship, ma'am.
呃 法兹夫人
Uh, Mrs. Fuzz.
哦 亲爱的
Oh, honey.
小东西有时能从大爆炸中生还
Little things sometimes survive big explosions.
等我们找到他 我要问他点事
And when we find him, I have questions.
好了 刚刚我们聊到哪了
Now, what are we talking about?
既然你问了
I'm glad you asked.
我正要让小队知道
I was just letting the team know.
管控给我们发了活
Control has a job for us.
我的理智已经向我
My better judgment has been
尖叫整整两天了
screaming at me for two days now.
它一直告诉我 你们会害我丢掉工作
It keeps saying that you lot are gonna cost me my job.
说不定呢
We might.
那得是她
She might.
我告诉我的理智闭嘴
I told my judgment to shut up
去睡一觉
and take a nap.
因为我们还有工作要做
'Cause we have work to do.
有人去过图尔卡纳IV星*吗
Has anybody been to Turkana IV?
（* 未来《下一代》4x06的故事正发生在此）
等下 你说的是图尔卡纳还是朱尔娜娜
Wait. Did you say Turkana or say Jur-Jurnana?
他以为是「你妈四星」
He thought "Your Mama IV."
你妈四星
Oh, Your Mama IV.
星际迷航中国字幕组译制
翻译: 瓦肯蔬菜汤
翻译: 北窗高卧久息尘
翻译: Soulzt
翻译: 舟行万里1234
翻译: 是大e呀
翻译: 诺北
校对: narwhrl
时间轴: narwhrl